adsanddeals.com 2018-05-12

# Privacy Policy | AdsandDeals.com

This Privacy Statement sets out our privacy policies and practices with respect to the collection, use and disclosure of personal information in connection with [www.adsanddeals.com](http://www.adsanddeals.com/) (the "Site"). This Privacy Policy may be updated by us giving reasonable notice of the revised terms by posting on the Site, and this Privacy Policy may be supplemented or modified by agreements entered into between us and you from time to time. 

"personal information" means any information about an identifiable individual, as further defined under applicable laws.

**COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

The Site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (such as name address and email address) and demographic information (such as postal code, age, or other information which we may request from time to time) and other information that is used by us to provide services. We use the customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information that he or she has requested regarding the Site or regarding services offered by us.

This Site uses an ad form for customers to place online and/or print ads. One of the express purposes of the Site is to gather contact information provided voluntarily by customers to be published either online or in print, as the case may be, and in connection with items that are for sale by customers. We have no control over who views online or print ads. Contact information provided may be used to contact customers when necessary. Please do not post any personal information on the Site that you expect to keep private. 

We do not store credit card information. Credit card transactions are transmitted to a financial gateway, and we endeavor to protect the security of your payment information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology.

Demographic and profile data is also collected at the Site. We use this data to tailor each visitor's experience at the Site, showing the user content that we think he or she might be interested in, and displaying the content according to the user's preferences.

We may use customer information for additional purposes that may be identified at or before the time that the information is collected. We also use information from customers for accounting and transaction completion purposes.

**OTHER DATA WE COLLECT**

All classified and forum postings are stored in our database, even after "deletion," and may be archived elsewhere.

Our web logs and other records are stored indefinitely

**Disclosure of Personal Information**

WE MAY SELL OR RENT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES FOR THEIR MARKETING PURPOSES WITHOUT USERS EXPLICIT CONSENT. BY USING THE SITE IN ANY WAY, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THESE TERMS OF USE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS OF USE, DO NOT USE THE SITE.

We may further disclose certain personal information as follows:  
•   \- to third party service providers and to affiliated entities in order to carry out work on our behalf,   
•   \- to law enforcement agencies for the purposes of investigating fraud or other offences, or   
•   \- to legal, financial, and other professional advisors or in connection with the sale or reorganization of all or part of its business or operations. 

Except as provided above, we will not use or disclose personal information for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with the consent of the individual or as required or permitted by law.

**Cookies and IP Addresses**   
We use your IP address to help identify you and your membership, gather broad demographic information about our users, diagnose problems with our server, and administer the Site. The Site uses cookies to keep track of your membership tools. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password. We also provide an option to log out should you be using an insecure or publicly shared computer.

We use outside ad companies to display ads on the Site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of the Site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information.

**Links**   
The Site may contain features and functionalities that may link you or provide you with access to third party content that is completely independent of us, including web sites, directories, servers, networks, systems, information and databases, applications, software, programs, products or services, and the Internet as a whole.

Your interactions with organizations and/or individuals found on or through the Site, including payment and delivery of goods or services, and any other terms, conditions, warranties or representations associated with such transactions or communications, are solely between you and such organizations and/or individuals. You should make whatever investigation you feel necessary or appropriate before proceeding with any online or offline transaction or communications with any of these third parties. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. Please ensure you review the privacy policies of the websites that you visit.

**ABOUT SSL CERTIFICATES**   
**Security**   
It is possible that any information transmitted via the Internet may be intercepted by unknown third parties. We cannot guarantee complete security. 

We use Verisign to have credit card data transmitted to our network servers in a secure encrypted mode.

**Opt-Out**   
When appropriate, users of the Site are given the opportunity to (i) opt-out of receiving communications from us, (ii) remove their information from our database, or (iii) elect to no longer receive services from us. If you wish to opt-out of receiving further communications, please contact our privacy officer (the �Privacy Officer�) by email or mail using the contact information provided below. This opt-out is not binding on any third part who may have previously obtained your contact information. 

**Corrections/Contact**   
Users of this Site may contact the Privacy Officer to modify or correct any of their personal information that is under our control. An individual may also direct a written complaint regarding compliance with this Privacy Statement to the Privacy Officer and, within a reasonable time upon receiving the written complaint, the Privacy Officer will conduct an investigation into the matter. Within a reasonable time of concluding the investigation, the Privacy Officer will inform the complainant whether the complaint will be allowed or denied. If the Privacy Officer allows the complaint, we will take appropriate measure necessary to rectify the source of the complaint.

**Contact Us**   
If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, our privacy practices in connection with this Site, or our collection, use, disclosure, or retention of your personal information in connection with this Site, please contact the Privacy Officer as follows: 

AdsAndDeals.com   
Attention: Privacy Officer 

Email: privacyofficer@adsanddeals.com
